[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 5 \u00d7 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "62",
      "options": [
        "62",
        "67",
        "64",
        "60"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 1 \u00d7 8?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "options": [
        "17",
        "14",
        "10",
        "12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 8 + 8 \u00d7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "24",
      "options": [
        "22",
        "26",
        "29",
        "24"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 13 + 1 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "14",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "12",
        "19",
        "16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 9 + 5 \u00d7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "24",
      "options": [
        "22",
        "24",
        "29",
        "26"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 12 + 10 \u00d7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "52",
      "options": [
        "54",
        "57",
        "50",
        "52"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 8 + 9 \u00d7 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "62",
      "options": [
        "60",
        "62",
        "64",
        "67"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 8 + 8 \u00d7 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "88",
      "options": [
        "88",
        "90",
        "86",
        "93"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 8 + 7 \u00d7 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "50",
      "options": [
        "52",
        "55",
        "50",
        "48"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 16 + 7 \u00d7 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "79",
      "options": [
        "79",
        "77",
        "84",
        "81"
      ]
    }
]